<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LifeFirst_App</string>
    <string name="title_activity_homepage">homepage</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="describe_one">“Life First” provides everything in one platform.
        It is a project which has come forward to help in this COVID-19 crisis.
        Amidst the rise of the COVID-19 cases, Life First has come forward to meet the demand for oxygen supply in our country.
        We are doing our best to make sure all the COVID-19 patients are treated.
        We are also creating awareness among people to donate plasma.
        Life first collaborated with the team that can provide everything in this COVID-19 crisis.
        Life First came into existence in 2021.
         <br/>
        LIFE FIRST WHERE THE LIFE OF AN INDIVIDUAL IS A TOP PRIORITY.
         <br/>A RAY OF HOPE AND A HOPE OF LIFE.
        <b>LIFE FIRST (JAAN HAI TO JAHAANH HAI). YOUR LIFE MATTERS. </b></string>
    <string name="describe_two">“To inspire hope and contribute to health and well-being by the best care to every patient through integrated clinical education and research.”
<b>CARE, ACHIEVE, INNOVATE :</b>
        Our focus is on providing and improving quality of care,  including patient experience, safety, and outcomes, while embracing innovation to deliver enhanced productivity and improved services.
<b>Primary Goals :</b>
To create an environment where the whole community gets sensitized about health.
To ensure the availability of primary health care to each and every individual.
    </string>

    <string name="describe_three">
Our Organization is committed to provide basic amenities in the underserved areas and work as a catalyst for providing sustainable means of livelihood through providing healthcare services, educating, training, capacity building, and empowering the needy sections of the society.

OUR VISION TO BE A NATIONAL AND INTERNATIONAL LEADER IN HEALTHCARE.

We will ensure that all we provide our patients receive the very best care possible and so our ambition is to provide care that compares with the best.</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
</resources>